Listen a minute .com
Actors Being an actor must be great.
I really wish I could act.
I'd love to have the confidence to act in front of people.
Being a member of the audience at the theatre is great, but acting on stage is better.
I wonder what it's like to be a movie star.
I think you need to be beautiful or handsome to be a successful Hollywood or Bollywood actor.
They all look great.
Actors are very lucky.
They get paid huge amounts of money to do what they love doing.
My favourite actors are all dead now.
I really like the actors in the old black and white movies.
They all looked so cool.
Actors in the old days seemed to be more glamorous than today's actors.
The best thing about being an actor is that all of your friends are famous too.